Victoria Juszkiewicz

Front-end Developer

Front-end Developer with 5 years of social media manager experience combining my technical and social media skills to build tech solutions that have a real positive impact on the user. I am tech savvy, love using tech solutions for many day-to-day problems and would love to contribute to building such products that make people's day-to-day better.

Email +48 690 401 001 <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>GitHub</u>

EXPERIENCE

CodeOp, Barcelona — Full Stack Developer

January 2023 - March 2023

- 3 months intensive full-time bootcamp covering full stack technologies: JavaScript ES6+, React.js, ReactContext API, Node/Express and MySQL, HTML and CSS
- Built 3 full stack projects: an MVP, a Feature Extension and a Group Project

Goodwinsmith, Redfootshoes, Celebrity Waist Trainers (Remote)-Social Media Manager/Influencer Marketing/ Content Creator

July 2020 - November 2022

- Increased Instagram account engagement by 38% by building and executing a social media strategy through competitive research and platform determination,
- Reached up to 2.2M views on Tik Tok video for my clients by creating viral content, building a marketing strategy and building strong relationships with my clients,
- Successfully implemented influencer marketing and affiliate marketing strategies to increase sales,
- Reached 10k followers on the company's Instagram account within a timeframe of just 6 months,

Body Safety Ltd (Workwearexperts, Cargo workwear, Chemsplash) Dublin— Digital Marketing Specialist

August 2019 - May 2020

- Managed all social media channels (Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Linkedin, Tiktok).
 This required: measuring and reporting on the performance of all digital marketing campaigns, SEO and generation of inbound traffic, identifying Target Customers, analysing competitors strategies and building an efficient content strategy,
- Ensured design consistency between the website, social media channels and email marketing,
- Improved user experience and engagement by collaborating with the development team to define user needs and implement a new form design and website flow-resulting in reduced registration and purchasing time.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

React.js, Vue.js

HTML, CSS

Node.js / Express JavaScript

MySQL

Postman

GitHub, Git Bash

Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

JSON Web Token,

Bcrypt

User Interface Design UI

UX

Trello

Notion

Figma

EDUCATION

Full Stack Development Bootcamp - CodeOp January 2023 - March 2023

Professional Diploma in Digital Marketing -IBAT COLLEGE DUBLIN

NFQ Level 5 Certificate-HAIRDRESSER SCHOOL POLAND

Spectrum Print Logistic Dublin— Quality Control

May 2015 - April 2016 and February 2017 - August 2019

- Ensured team efficiency by managing task distribution, monitoring and evaluating workers performance
- Ensured team safety by instructing new employees on safety measures and making sure that work equipment is available

LANGUAGES

Polish (Native)

English (Fluent)

PROJECTS

Group Project

- Full stack app that reduces food waste and cooking time by finding recipes based on the user input ingredients (things that they have in the fridge)
- Main Features: search recipes by ingredients, user authentication and a list of favourites recipes for each user
- Built with: MySQL, React js, Node js, Bootstrap, CSS, JavaScript, bcypt, JSON Web Tokens (JWT), API, React-toastify, Figma, Postman

MVP 2

- Full stack app that displays trending movies
- Main features: User can create an account and log in, user can browse trending movies
- Built with: MySQL, React, Node js, Postman, Mui, Bootstrap, JavaScript

MVP

- Full stack app that connects pets with their future owners
- People can search by type & location and rescue a life companion Allowing users to find pets with a search function on the front end that loads data from Petfinder API
- Built with: React, CSS, Bootstrap, Postman, Petfinder API, Javascript